United University Professions (UUP); Records apap039
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Labor Relations-Correspondence, 1972-1993; VII; 2.0 cubic ft.
  - Governor's Office of Employee Relations [RESTRICTED], 1974 July-1993 December; 1; 1.0 cubic ft.
    - Hartnett, Thomas F. (Director) [RESTRICTED], 1985 August-1985 August (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 8)
    - Hartnett, Thomas F. (Director) [RESTRICTED], 1985 September-1987 September (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 9)
    - Hodes, Nancy (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], 1976 November; 1979 June-1981 August; 1982 May; 1984 November; 1987 May; 1986 July (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 10)
    - Kershaw, Leonard (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], 1974 July-1977 June (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 11)
    - Kershaw, Leonard (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], 1977 July-1979 October (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 12)
    - Kurach, Ronald (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], 1981 February-1985 January (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 13)
    - Moore, Elizabeth (Director) [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1989 May; 1990 March-1990 December (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 14)
    - Northrop, James B. (Acting Director; Deputy Director) [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1979 May; 1981 February-1981 May (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 15)
    - Rowan, Michael (Employee Relations Assistant; Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], 1987 January-1993 May (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 16)
    - Rudden, Maria R. (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], 1985 March-1987 July (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 17)
    - Wollett, Donald (Director) [RESTRICTED], 1975 April-1977 September (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 18)
    - Wollett, Donald (Director) [RESTRICTED], 1977 October-1978 June (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 19)
    - Other Correspondents and OER Policy Statements [RESTRICTED], 1974 December-1991 September (Box VII.1.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 20)
  - SUNY [RESTRICTED], 1972 August-1993 June; 2; 1.0 cubic ft.
    Primarily outgoing correspondence from UUP's President, Executive Director (later Director of Staff) and Associate Director of Staff to representatives at SUNY Central Administration, including the Chancellor, Director of Employee Relations, Employee Relations Associates, and the Vice Chancellors of various areas including Academic Affairs, University Affairs, Employee Relations and Personnel, and Faculty and Staff Relations. The correspondence in this series requested SUNY to investigate practices on specific campuses that UUP objected to or requested clarification on. A wide gamut of issues were covered, such as the application of SUNY policies from one campus to another, vacancy announcements listing below minimum salaries, attendance reporting systems implemented on campuses, the ranking of professional positions, discretionary salary increases, concerns with building security on a campus, and SUNY's patent policy to name just a few.
    The correspondence also documents UUP's requests to SUNY for assistance for individual members encountering problems with insurance coverage, salary increases not reflected in paychecks, and receiving confirmations that temporary appointments have been changed to continuing appointments. There is also correspondence setting up labor-management meetings and listing the issues to be discussed. Also occasionally included are copies of SUNY policies, either issued to all campuses or memoranda sent to the SUNY Board of Trustees. For the most part, however, referenced attachments to outgoing UUP correspondence are not included.
    Additional correspondence between SUNY and UUP can be found in some of the project and subject files in the collection, particularly those of Samuel Wakshull in Series 3 of Subgroup III. The materials in this series are organized by the name of the SUNY representative involved. Each individual's title is indicated in the folder title. The "other correspondents" at the end of the series are for other SUNY representatives for whom there was not a substantial amount of correspondence and who were initially filed in "general" or "miscellaneous" SUNY correspondence files. Included in these latter folders are some materials dealing with a SUNY Women's Conference held in 1986.
    - Albro, Donna Harshaw (Employee Relations Associate) [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1978 September (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 1)
    - Burke, Joseph (Provost; Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs) [RESTRICTED], 1988 May; 1991 February; 1992 September (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 2)
    - Decker, Janice (Employee Relations Associate) [RESTRICTED], 1977 February (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 3)
    - Dullea, Henrick (Associate Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations and Personnel) [RESTRICTED], 1982 October-1982 November (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 4)
    - Gillman, Richard (Acting Vice Chancellor University Affairs and Development) [RESTRICTED], 1979 May-1979 July (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 5)
    - Haines, Raymond L., Jr. (Employee Relations Associate) [RESTRICTED], 1980 July-1981 May (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 6)
    - Haines, Raymond L., Jr. (Director of Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1987 February-1990 December (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 7)
    - Hines, Thomas (Employee Relations Associate) [RESTRICTED], 1977 August-1977 September (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 8)
    - Hodes, Nancy (Employee Relations Associate; Director of Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1976 March-1979 February (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 9)
    - Johnstone, Bruce D. (Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1988 August-1991 December; 1993 June (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 10)
    - Katz, Lawrence (Personnel Associate; Director of Employee Benefits) [RESTRICTED], 1977 June-1980 November (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 11)
    - Kelly, James F. (Acting Chancellor; Executive Vice Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1976 October; 1978 February (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 12)
    - Kimberly, Michael (Assistant Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1976 December-1980 May (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 13)
    - Komisar, Jerome B. (Vice Chancellor for Faculty and Staff Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1975 September-1978 December; 1980 July-1981 April (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 14)
    - Komisar, Jerome B. (Executive Vice Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1985 May-1990 April (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 15)
    - Mannix, Thomas M. (Associate Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations and Personnel) [RESTRICTED], 1986 June; 1987 February-1993 February (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 16)
    - Mason, Karen A. (Personnel Associate) [RESTRICTED], 1979 October (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 17)
    - Naples, Caesar J. (Assistant Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1975 May-1976 June (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 18)
    - Penney, Sherry H. (Vice Chancellor for Academic Programs and Planning) [RESTRICTED], 1984 July-1986 July (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 19)
    - Peterson, Thomas J. Jr. (Assistant Vice Chancellor for Academic Personnel; Acting Vice Chancellor for Faculty and Staff Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1976 February; 1977 February-1980 August (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 20)
    - Schmidt, Dolores (Assistant Vice Chancellor for Affirmative Action) [RESTRICTED], 1977 December-1978 February; 1980 July; 1982 May-1982 August; 1986 June (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 21)
    - Smoot, James S. (Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations and Educational Services) [RESTRICTED], 1983 May-1985 January (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 22)
    - Villa, Joyce Yaple (Director of Employee Relations; Assistant Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1979 November-1983 August (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 23)
    - Villa, Joyce Yaple (Director of Employee Relations; Assistant Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1983 September-1992 September (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 24)
    - Wharton, Clifton (Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1977 October-1981 July (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 25)
    - Wharton, Clifton (Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1981 August-1983 September (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 26)
    - Wharton, Clifton (Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1986 January-1987 January (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 27)
    - Other Correspondents (Kevin Berry, UUP Executive Director file) [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 28)
    - Other Correspondents [RESTRICTED], 1972 August-1982 September (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 29)
    - Other Correspondents (including 1986 correspondence on SUNY Women's Conference) [RESTRICTED], 1982 October-1983 November; 1986 October-1986 November (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 30)
    - Other Correspondents [RESTRICTED], 1987 March-1988 October (Box VII.2.1 (VII-Labor Relations-Correspond), Folder 31)
- Communications, 1973-2000; VIII; 21.35 cubic ft.
  Arranged in ten series.
  - Series 1:The Connection, 1987 September-2000 June; 11.1; 0.20 cubic ft.
    A single page, two-sided newsletter for chapter leaders, chapter newsletter editors, delegates, Executive Board members, and committee members, printed approximately monthly on an academic year basis (i.e., September to June). As of the late 1990s, the circulation of The Connection was approximately one thousand, but chapter newsletter editors are permitted and explicitly encouraged to reprint any materials. Topics receiving regular attention include negotiations updates; member benefits information; SUNY system issues, including the SUNY budget; information on upcoming meetings and Delegate Assemblies; reports on campus specific issues of interest and/or concern to all; reports on political activism and lobbying activities; information on advertising campaigns; upcoming NYSUT and AFT conventions; and information on grant opportunities.
    For earlier versions of communications between UUP and its leadership, see the issues of For Your Information in Series 4 of Subgroup II and the Leadership Bulletins in the subject files for the Wakshull Administration in Subseries 3.1 of Subgroup III.
    - Volume 1, Nos. 1-10, 1987 September-1988 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 1)
    - Volume 2, Nos. 1-11, 1988 August-1989 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 2)
    - Volume 3, Nos. 1-9, 1989 September-1990 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 3)
    - Volume 4, Nos. 1-9, 1990 September-1991 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 4)
    - Volume 5, Nos. 1-9, 1991 September-1992 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 5)
    - Volume 6, Nos. 1-9, 1992 September-1993 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 6)
    - Volume 7, Nos. 1-9, 1993 September-1994 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 7)
    - Volume 8, Nos. 1-9, 1994 September-1995 July (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 8)
    - Volume 9, Nos. 1-8, 1995 September-1996 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 9)
    - Volume 10, Nos. 1-8, 1996 September-1997 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 10)
    - Volume 11, Nos. 1-9, 1997 September-1998 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 11)
    - Volume 12, Nos. 1-9, 1998 September-1999 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 12)
    - Volume 13, Nos. 1-9, 1999 September-2000 June (Box VIII.1.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 13)
  - Series 2:The Voice, 1973 May-2000 May/June; 11.2; 1.53 cubic ft.
    The Voice is the official publication of UUP distributed to all members of the bargaining unit. In addition, complimentary copies are distributed to top-level members of SUNY management, lawmakers, and news media organizations in the state. Published on an academic year basis (i.e., each volume runs roughly from August or September to May or June), The Voice regularly carries candidate statements, information on statewide and Delegate Assembly elections, the annual audit, attendance reports for affiliate conventions, and verbatim text of negotiations proposals made by both the State and UUP. Regularly featured topics include contract negotiations with the State of New York; Executive Board activities; chapter events and issues; the SUNY budget and legislative issues affecting SUNY and higher education; increases in membership; advertising campaigns; feature articles on particular campuses, and/or specific departments or individuals on campus; information on candidates UUP endorses for state and national offices; and messages from UUP's leadership, including columns by UUP's President and reports on the President's activities.
    The Voice also carries photographs of Delegate Assemblies, lobbying activities and rallies, negotiations and other meetings, and individual officers and members. In fall 1998 [volume 26] The Voice changed from a newspaper format to a news magazine layout, and became more theme-related with a series of articles devoted to each issue's main theme, such as the concerns of part-time employees, women and the labor movement, academic freedom, and SUNY-specific features such as technology, the performing arts, and athletics on SUNY campuses. A few of the earliest volumes of The Voice are incomplete.
    Arranged chronologically by size.
    - Volume 5, Nos. 1-9, 1976 October-1977 July (Box VIII.2.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 1)
    - Volume 9, No. 10, 1981 August (Box VIII.2.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 2)
    - Volume 10, Nos. 1-8, 1981 October-1982 September (Box VIII.2.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 3)
    - Volume 11, Nos. 1-7, 1982 October-1983 June (Box VIII.2.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 4)
    - Volume 12, Nos. 1-8, 1984 July-1984 August (Box VIII.2.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 5)
    - Volume 13, Nos. 1-3, 5-6, 1984 September-1984 December; 1985 April-1985 June (Box VIII.2.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 6)
    - Volume 6, Nos. 1-10, 1977 August-1978 July (Box VIII.2.2 (VIII-Communications), Folder 1)
    - Volume 7, Nos. 1-10, 1978 September-1979 August (Box VIII.2.2 (VIII-Communications), Folder 2)
    - Volume 8, Nos. 1-10, 1979 September-1980 July (Box VIII.2.2 (VIII-Communications), Folder 3)
    - Volume 9, Nos. 1-9, 1980 September-1981 May (Box VIII.2.2 (VIII-Communications), Folder 4)
      No. 10 filed separately-Box VIII.2.5.
    - Volume 13, No. 4, 1985 February-1985 March (Box VIII.2.2 (VIII-Communications), Folder 5)
    - Volume 14, Nos. 1-7, 1985 September-1986 July (Box VIII.2.3 (VIII-Communications), Folder 1)
    - Volume 15, Nos. 1-16, 1986 September-1988 July (Box VIII.2.3 (VIII-Communications), Folder 2)
    - Volume 16, Nos. 1-9, 1988 September-1989 June (Box VIII.2.3 (VIII-Communications), Folder 3)
    - Volume 17, Nos. 1-10, 1989 September-1990 June (Box VIII.2.3 (VIII-Communications), Folder 4)
    - Volume 18, Nos. 1-9, 1990 September-1991 May (Box VIII.2.3 (VIII-Communications), Folder 5)
    - Volume 19, Nos. 1-9, 1991 September-1992 May (Box VIII.2.3 (VIII-Communications), Folder 6)
    - Volume 20, Nos. 1-9, 1992 September-1993 May (Box VIII.2.4 (VIII-Communications), Folder 1)
    - Volume 21, Nos. 1-9, 1993 September-1994 May (Box VIII.2.4 (VIII-Communications), Folder 2)
    - Volume 22, Nos. 1-9, 1994 September-1995 May (Box VIII.2.4 (VIII-Communications), Folder 3)
    - Volume 23, Nos. 1-9, 1995 September-1996 May (Box VIII.2.4 (VIII-Communications), Folder 4)
    - Volume 24, Nos. 1-9, 1996 September-1997 May (Box VIII.2.4 (VIII-Communications), Folder 5)
    - Volume 25, Nos. 1-9, 1997 September-1998 May (Box VIII.2.4 (VIII-Communications), Folder 6)
    - Volume 1, Nos. 1-12, 1973 May-1974 May (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 1)
    - Volume 2, Nos. 1-12, 1974 June-1975 May (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 2)
    - Volume 3, Nos. 1-6 (8 issues total), 1975 June-1976 Summer (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 3)
    - Volume 4, No. 1, 1976 September (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 4)
    - Volume 5, Nos. 1-9, 1976 October-1977 July; (photocopies) (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 5)
    - Volume 9, No. 10, 1981 August; (photocopy) (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 6)
    - Volume 10, Nos. 1-8, 1981 October-1982 September; (photocopies) (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 7)
    - Volume 11, Nos. 1-7, 1982 October-1983 June; (photocopies) (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 8)
    - Volume 12, Nos. 1-8, 1983 August-1984 July (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 9)
    - Volume 13, Nos. 1-3, 5-6, 1984 September-1985 June (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 10)
    - Volume 26, Nos. 1-9, 1998 September-1999 June (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 11)
    - Volume 27, Nos. 1-9, 1999 September-2000 June (Box VIII.2.5 (VIII-Communications), Folder 12)
  - News Releases, 1977 February-2000 June; 2A; 0.33 cubic ft.
    Press releases distributed by UUP. Topics include upcoming Delegate Assemblies; resolutions adopted at Delegate Assemblies; election results for UUP statewide officers; awards given by UUP, such as the Link Scholarship, Friend of SUNY Award, and Nina Mitchell Award; commencement and completion of contract negotiations as well as delays in negotiations and critical issues in negotiations; commentary of UUP regarding SUNY and State of New York actions (for example, the state budget or the appointment of a new Chancellor) that impact SUNY; UUP-sponsored conferences and events; and other issues that UUP wished to make its position clear on. See Subgroup II UUP Predecessors and Early UUP Years, Series 2 SPA/UUP Administrative Office General Office Files for news releases prior to 1977.
    - News Releases, 1977 February-1983 February (Box VIII.2A.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 1)
    - News Releases, 1985 June; 1986 October-1989 October (Box VIII.2A.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 2)
    - News Releases, 1989 December-1992 October (Box VIII.2A.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 3)
    - News Releases, 1993 February-1995 January (Box VIII.2A.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 4)
    - News Releases, 1995 February-1996 June (Box VIII.2A.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 5)
    - News Releases, 1996 October-1998 June (Box VIII.2A.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 6)
    - News Releases, 1998 October-2000 June (Box VIII.2A.1 (VIII-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1978-2000; 3; 1.03 cubic ft.
    - Legislative Ad Campaigns, 1985; 1989-2000; 3.1; 0.20 cubic ft.
      Advertisements produced by UUP to coincide with sessions of the state legislature and to raise public awareness of SUNY's needs. Campaigns often focused on the impact of budget cuts on SUNY students and the impact the SUNY system has on the future of New York State. Some "legislative giveaways" carrying the legislative campaign message, as well as some oversized versions of various campaigns are included with the memorabilia in Series 9 of this Subgroup. Television and radio advertisements that accompanied various advertising campaigns are included in the video and audio tapes in Series 6 of this Subgroup. Tentative dates were assigned for some of the materials in this subseries based on information provided by members of UUP's Communications Department.
      - "Employers in New York have the SUNY advantage", ca. February 1985 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 1)
      - "We're solving one of the most urgent problems of our time: the affordable education", ca. February 1985 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 2)
      - "Who's Giving Whom the Business?", March 1985 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 3)
      - "New York, You Can't Have it Both Ways", January 1989 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 4)
      - "If You Really Love NY, Don't Cut the SUNY Budget", February 1989 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 5)
      - "We made a promise to the next generation-Can our state afford to break it?", February/March 1989; January 1990 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 6)
      - "Cancelled-How smart can New York be if we keep cutting classes?", March 1989 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 7)
      - "They're Cutting Out Classes...", March 1989 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 8)
      - "Get Smart, New York. Invest in SUNY", March 1990 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 9)
      - "Cancelled: Will SUNY Be There for the Next Generation?", December 1990 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 10)
      - Resolution condemning Gov. Cuomo on trying to break state employee union contracts, December 1990 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 11)
      - "Get the Facts", pre-1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 12)
      - "Nobody likes to pay higher taxes. But the alternatives are worse...", ca. 1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 13)
      - "Shortchanging higher education is bad business", March 1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 14)
      - "Cutting SUNY is the no-brain approach to solving our state's problems", March 1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 15)
      - "Slamming the door at SUNY slams the door on our state's future", May 1991; August 1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 16)
      - "State University of New York: Our Future Depends on It", January 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 17)
      - "SUNY: New York's Future Depends on It", January 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 18)
      - "Denied Admission", January/February 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 19)
      - "Going, Going, Gone", March 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 20)
      - "SUNY's Future in Question: You Hold the Answer", May 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 21)
      - "Time is Running Out", June 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 22)
      - "Sign and mail this letter Now-Your kid's future is at stake", ca. 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 23)
      - "Under Destruction: It's time to say...No More Cuts", (Stony Brook Chapters funded), ca. 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 24)
      - "A Smaller SUNY Means a Smaller New York", January 1993 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 25)
      - "Endangered Species: Invest in SUNY", January-March 1993 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 26)
      - "Infrastructure: Invest in SUNY", January-March 1993 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 27)
      - "Invest in Futures", January/February 1994 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 28)
      - "Chain Reaction: Break the Chain. Restore SUNY Funding", January/February 1995 (Box VIII.3.1.1 (3.1-Legislative Ad Campaigns), Folder 29)